Episode 7 "You're So Close, I Think You May Make Me Dizzy"
Two months ago,
Lady Anastasia got into a carriage
rented by Baron Shaderan
and headed for Granado Castle.
For a few days, she traveled in peace,
then we're told that near the royal
capital, she was set upon by bandits.
While Lady Anastasia was
desperately trying to escape...
she fell into the river, which
had swollen with the rain.
The driver tried to rescue her,
but wounds inflicted by the
bandits made it impossible.
The carriage was destroyed,
and everything it carried was stolen.
This summary of the incident is
based on the driver's testimony
and the police investigation.
Lady Anastasia's body hasn't been found,
but they believe the chance
of her survival is dismal.
But the letter from her little brother...
"Elder sister is already home."
If Miss Anastasia is alive,
won't Lady Marie try to distance
herself from Lord Kyros?
The master's love for her is good and true.
Which means that it is necessary
for someone to play the villain.
Y-You don't mean that you'll do
something to Miss Anastasia...
No.
The master has forbidden me
from using violent methods.
I won't do anything extreme.
Well, not overly so.
Wh-What does "not overly so"
mean? Can I just go home now?
"Companions enrich a journey"
is a favorite proverb of mine.
Besides...
it's possible that more than just
snakes will dart from the underbrush.
A few days after Mio left...
Marie, starting today, I'll be your
attendant. I look forward to serving.
What?
Oh. As you might expect, the maid
uniforms aren't sized to fit me.
Th-That wasn't my concern.
A lady's maid is relied upon in an
emotional sense as well, right?
Well...
We do spend a lot of time together, so
it is easy to feel rather close to them.
That's it.
Marie, I want to become the
person you get along with best.
That's why I decided to
become your attendant.
His eyes are so clear.
What do you think? Well done
for my first time, isn't it?
Y-Yes. Thank you.
All right. Next is your dress, correct?
What? He can't mean that he'll dress me!
I couldn't endure that! I'll die!
What do you say? If you don't have
a particular one in mind, I'll—
You broke your promise!
I said I'd dress her, didn't I?!
Th-That's no reason to come flying at me!
Master, you just want to touch
Marie, don't you? You lecher!
Cillie has been quite disrespectful.
However, Master, the closeness
that makes you happy
seems to be a level of closeness
that makes Lady Marie nervous.
One should temper one's eagerness.
The Next Day
Marie, let's go on a date!
What?
This morning, a letter arrived from Luiphon.
He writes, "I've prepared a tremendous gift
for you, so please come to the royal capital."
Third Prince
Though, knowing him,
I wouldn't expect too much.
And so...
Will you go out with me? Just the two of us?
Yes!
Those kind of clothes are
nice, too. You look lovely.
Thank you, Lord Kyros.
You look wonderful as well.
Thank you.
But if you talk like that,
people will find out who I am.
Call me just "Kyros," with no title.
What? What?!
There's still time before our
appointment with Luiphon.
Let's go look around at everything first.
If we get separated or lost, then this rare
chance at a date will be ruined, right?
Th-Then, shall—
Let's go, Kyros.
This is where Lady Marie is from?
In the Shaderan lands, aside from
largely wheat-based farming,
raising cattle makes up the
majority of the industry.
Really? I'd heard they were poor,
so I imagined a small, dried-up village.
It's good land.
However, after the war, taxes were
levied according to a region's size,
so they've had to continue
cultivating large swathes of land.
Maintaining the land and rotation
of use is a lord's job,
but it doesn't appear to be done well here.
Um, where are we?
Lady Marie's old school.
What?
I haven't seen you before.
Are you a new student?
Well, I came from the royal capital
to learn about farming, you see.
And I was thinking that I'd like
to ask the students here about it.
Are there any girls here?
Well, up until last year, the daughter of
Baron Shaderan attended our school, but now...
Oh my! A baron's daughter?
I couldn't possibly!
Isn't there anyone who's graduated
that I could speak to more casually?
I believe the daughter of the
local innkeeper also attended,
but she found work in the royal
capital, and withdrew mid-term.
I think her name was Karina.
That serves my purposes quite nicely.
Yes? May I ask who you are?
You are Karina Burton's mother, correct?
I am a detective from the capital.
The truth is, your daughter may have
gotten caught up in a certain incident.
What?!
I need to check your daughter's student
identification from when she attended school.
If possible, I'd like to
borrow it for a while.
Th-There should be limits to this nonsense.
I didn't lie.
Unlike the police, being a detective is a
job where calling yourself one makes you one.
But you talked about some kind of incident.
A baron's daughter, thought to have died
in an accident, may still be alive.
That's quite the incident, isn't it?
And the possibility that Karina
Burton is involved isn't zero.
You're being reckless, Miss Mio.
Please don't worry.
The big lies begin now.
No! You're scaring me!
The Shaderan residence is just over there.
Please be careful not to
expose your background.
Um, shouldn't we discuss
this before we do it?
Please adapt as we go.
I'll just keep quiet the whole time.
This is an impressive mansion!
Yes, it is. However, it isn't
being managed very well.
It wasn't this bad previously, but...
Miss Mio?!
Hey! Who are you?
If you're tradesmen, go around the back!
You aren't debt collectors, are you?
I'm Karina! This is my fiancé, Henry!
This is my friend's house, and when we
arrived, the gate was open, so we came in!
Sorry!
What?
I just told you! I'm dear Marie's friend!
A friend? Of that raggedy girl?
I met Marie in the capital! We went to
the same school, so we became friends.
It's true, that girl is supposedly
at the capital right now.
When I said I'd be visiting home,
she asked me if I'd come and
pick up something she'd wanted.
Miss, will you let me
into dear Marie's room?
Make sure you leave as soon as you're done.
This is it.
That girl was never good at the basics.
Cooking and cleaning took her so
long she never really finished,
so she started sleeping here.
Why did Marie have to work so hard?
Because she wasn't the least bit cute.
A woman with no prospect
of marriage has to work.
Then, when did she stop being cute?
She's been like that since she was born!
Compared with Lady Anastasia, she's
impertinent and completely unlovable.
Her grandmother, Lady Sasha, was the one
person who showed her some affection.
Sasha...
Big Sis Marie?!
H-Huh?
Cedric!
What are you doing?
Who are you two?
Baron Shaderan.
Pleased to meet you! I'm Karina Burton!
Dear Marie is my friend!
I now understand what brought
the two of you here, but...
That Tania! She loves her jokes!
This is a storage shed, isn't it?
It couldn't possibly be
my darling Marie's room.
What?
I'll show you to the mansion.
Cedric!
You go back to your room
and continue your studies!
Y-Yes, sir.
This is the first time a friend
of Marie's has visited us.
She's a bookworm, and so shy.
Don't you find her a bit gloomy?
What? Marie is so cheerful and
kind, everyone loves her!
I see. As her father,
I'm happy to hear that.
By the way, what is it that
you've come to pick up?
It's something precious to
a girl, so it's a secret.
She asked me to look for it.
Go right in. This is Marie's room.
What? So she did have a
proper room after all!
Oh, are you playing tricks on us too, Baron?
This is her sister's room, isn't it?
What makes you think that?
Dear Marie loves to study.
It'd be odd if her room didn't
have bookshelves in it!
That's...
Now, stop playing silly
pranks. You can't trick me.
Sorry about that! I really will
show you the way this time!
Here. This is Marie's room.
I'll leave, so search as much as you like.
Is this really Lady Marie's room?
What?
Wait! What are you doing?
Shh! Quiet.
Really? I'm so glad to hear it.
The wife's room seems
to be next to this one.
But...
That's so true, Anastasia.
My dear guests, I'm so sorry!
We're supposed to go out
as a family, you see.
Can I ask you to leave for today?
Oh, really? Well then,
we'll excuse ourselves here.
Oh, and when you get back,
could you tell Marie something for me?
If there's something she wants, she
should come back and get it herself.
That's so true! But dear Marie seems so busy.
After all, there's only a month left until
her betrothal ceremony to the count!
That may be true...
but if the ceremony hasn't happened,
then she isn't engaged.
That girl still belongs to me,
and I'm not letting anyone steal her.
Then, Marie must be very important to you.
I suppose so.
Oh my.
We have guests? I'll go and
prepare some tea right away.
No, they were just leaving.
And we're all going out.
Really? Then if you'll wait just a moment...
That's Lady Marie's mother?
Mama's going out now.
Be a good girl and wait,
won't you, Anastasia?
Well, enjoy your visit home.
I will! If you'll excuse us.
I broke out in a cold sweat.
We'll wait a bit, then return to the mansion.
What?!
Ow.
We're lucky that they didn't lock up.
Now, come before the maid notices.
M-Miss Mio, you are a maid, aren't you?
I am, without question, a maid. Why?
So you did survive... Lady Anastasia.
A-A doll?
Do you think that the shock of losing Miss
Anastasia drove Baroness Elvira insane?
No, she's sane.
She understands that it's just a doll.
It was made very recently.
Most likely by the baroness herself.
But it looks so much like a real person.
Well, the hair was real human hair.
Human hair?!
And the dress, too.
Using the police
investigations as reference,
there's no doubt she was wearing
that dress during the accident.
W-Wait. Miss Anastasia fell into the
river and her body wasn't found, right?
Then how did her hair and clothes...
Indeed. There are inconsistencies with the
events of the accident as we know them.
And if that's the case...
Please return us immediately.
There is someone I must meet with.
Do you mean...
The driver of the hired carriage... is lying.
Delicious!
So these are the flavors of Ipsandros.
I often came here while I was a student.
The food in the dormitory
was all too refined.
You attended the Royal Academy just
like Prince Luiphon, didn't you?
Yes.
From the age of twelve to the age of
eighteen, I attended and learned many things.
What a strange sort of feeling.
Lord Kyros was a young child once, too.
All right. For dessert, we'll have dondurma!
Dondurma? In Ipsian, that means
"a frozen thing," doesn't it?
Here you go!
There you go! Enjoy!
Th-Thank you.
What?
Wait! Oh!
PRECIOUS...
Please don't move!
Honestly! Please control yourself!
Of course!
Oh, it's chewy! It's quite delicious!
Kyros, would you like to have some... too?
Th-The cuteness is too much. It's killing me.
Honestly!
Th-This is incredible!
This shop handles goods from every country.
Foreign goods are popular
among merchants, you see.
Once you've tried Ips silk undergarments,
you'll never be able to wear any others.
You said that the first time we met, too.
Say, Kyros, will you allow me to buy
one thing for you as a present?
Lady Liu Liu paid me for helping with
writing letters and translating.
So if there's anything you'd like—
Well, that's a top-quality, one-of-a-kind
imported item, you see.
I-I didn't realize these were so costly.
Marie, does this suit me?
Y-Yes, it does. But I think the fancier
one there would suit you well, too.
Right then!
I'd like to try on the ones
that Marie mentioned!
All of them! I'll buy them all!
What?
What do you think?
How wonderful!
Flarian
student uniform
A student uniform? Where will you wear it?
I'll wear it to cheer you
up when you're down, Marie.
Right! I'll buy this, too!
What?!
It will probably still take a little
while for him to finish changing.
These are priced at a bargain.
This would be perfect for Lord Kyros!
Marie?
Sister?
Hey there.
What? Did I mishear before?
Miss, are you here alone?
How about a café if you haven't eaten?
Is he trying to get customers?
I'm sorry. I've already eaten.
Then, just some tea! My treat!
Wh-What is this all of a sudden?
I don't need tea. Please let go of me.
You are cute, aren't you?
He's forcing himself to
compliment me out of courtesy.
I should express my gratitude.
Oh, but...
I don't want to!
Help me, Lord Kyros!
What an unmannerly way to hit on someone.
When a lady says no, walk away.
Don't touch anyone without
their permission!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for causing trouble for you.
You have absolutely no reason to apologize!
But... didn't you realize that
he was trying to ask you out?
What?
It must have happened
many times before this.
N-No. My school was almost all boys,
but they never spoke to me more
than absolutely necessary.
They used to point at me and laugh.
That's not possible!
Even unadorned, you're so charming
that men would never leave you alone!
I'm not. I'm ugly, and my hair
and clothes are always raggedy.
Raggedy...
That's it! That's why they
kept her in tatters!
Baron Shaderan didn't want Marie's
charms known to anyone...
No! He wished to conceal it, even from her,
so he trapped her in that disgraceful state!
But... no matter how hard he tries
to tie Marie down, it won't work!
I'm never letting go.
Unlike those of other people,
Lord Kyros' hand is comforting.
It's so lonely without Marie here!
Stupid Master! It's no fair!
Now, now, Cillie.
Still, they are quite late
in returning, aren't they?
I hope nothing has happened.
Next time...
"A Gift More Lovely Than Jewels."
Episode 8 "A
Gift More Lovely Than Jewels"
If you don't watch, I'll send
you flying with a kick!
Now, Cillie!